(Sheldon:)You know, on Vulcan,
when your brother asks,
“Why are you hitting yourself?”
the answer is,
“I'm not.
You're moving my arm.”
(Sheldon:)To which he says,
“Fascinating.”
(Sheldon:)And then you both watch
educational television.
(quietly): Aw. When he says
things like that,
(Penny:)I just want to hug him
and make everything better.
(Leonard:)My brother was
mean to me, too.
(Penny:)Yeah, you probably
had it coming.
(Adam:)Do you have
any Spock collectibles?
(Sheldon:)I have many.
(Sheldon:)My most treasured
is an autographed napkin
(Sheldon:)given to me by my
very thoughtful friend Penny.
(Sheldon:)That's her over there.
Hi!
(Penny:)Look at that.
(Penny:)I'm in a movie,
my shirt stayed on.
(Adam:)Can we see the napkin?
(Sheldon:)Of course. Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)This will just take a moment.